A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Economic Reform Interests, Series F FA315
Rockefeller Archive Center
- National Trade Policy - Committee for a National Trade Policy - Rockefeller Family Contributions, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 0235A)
  Contributions by John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  DR material removed to Folder 235D.
- National Trade Policy - Committee for a National Trade Policy - Fund Raising, 1954-1956 (Box 27, Folder 0235B)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd served on fund raising committee; details of drive.
- National Trade Policy - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 0235C)
  Organized to promote a sound foreign economic policy, including tariff reductions. David Rockefeller 1953 contribution. Comments on activities. Reports of committee. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
- National Trade Policy - Committee for a National Trade Policy - Rockefeller Family Contributions, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 235)
  Contributions by David Rockefeller.
- National Trade Policy - Committee on Foreign Trade Education, Inc., 1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 236)
  Declination of appeals.
  54.1
  DR material removed to Folder 236A.
- National Trade Policy - Committee on Foreign Trade Education, Inc., 1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 0236A)
  One contribution by David Rockefeller, 1956; declination of other appeals. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
- National Trade Policy - Dallas Council on World Affairs, 1955-1960 (Box 27, Folder 237)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd spoke before council in 1960. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  54.3
  DR material removed to Folder 237A.
- National Trade Policy - Dallas Council on World Affairs, 1955-1960 (Box 27, Folder 0237A)
  David Rockefeller spoke before council in 1955. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
- National Trade Policy - Dallas Council on World Affairs - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Address, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 238)
  Preparations; text; comments on speech re population explosion.
- National Trade Policy - United States World Trade Fair, 1957-1961 (Box 28, Folder 239)
  Invitations to attend fairs all declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  54.5
- National Trade Policy - United States World Trade Fair, 1957-1961 (Box 28, Folder 0239A)
- National Trade Policy - American Committee for the United States-Japan Centennial, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 240)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd active in planning for celebration; Crown Prince and Princess tour of United States; reports on impact of tour. Dinners; publicity. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, D. C. Overton.
  54.6
- National Trade Policy - American Committee for the United States-Japan Centennial, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 241)
- National Trade Policy - American Committee for the United States-Japan Centennial, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 242)
- New York Board of Trade, 1920-1955 (Box 28, Folder 243)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. attended dinners; declined Gold Award; spoke at Rovensky dinner.
  106
- New York Board of Trade - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Address, 1951-1961 (Box 28, Folder 244)
  Invitations to dinners.
- New York Board of Trade - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Award, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 245)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd given Gold Award at Salute to Arts dinner; text of his speech.
- Committee for Economic Development, 1952-1961 (Box 28, Folder 246)
  Nelson A. Rockefeller contributions.
  197.1